走向极端。作为练习，我们会让大家夸张地模仿一个美国人。
Go to extremes. As an exercise, we have people put on a caricature of an American
口音，而且通常相当准确。不过，他们不愿意使用它，
accent, and generally it's quite accurate. They're reluctant, however, to use it
因为其中带着天然的模仿和自嘲。没关系，我可以保证，美国人
because of the inherent mockery involved. It's okay, I can assure you that Americans
当你故意装出非常夸张的美式口音时，他们甚至不会注意到。
won't even notice when you're putting on a super heavy American accent. They'll just
你的家人和朋友可能会产生负面反应，
think your English got better. Your family and friends may react negatively and make
他们可能会取笑你刚开始改变说话方式时还不成熟的尝试。
fun of your nascent attempts to modify your speech. way you are. They may think
他们可能觉得你的口音很可爱，也可能认为如果你改变说话方式，
that your accent is cute. They may think that if you change how you talk, you may
你也许会改变自己。关键是，你听起来会不一样，
change who you are. The bottom line is that you'll sound different and they may
我们建议你在陌生人面前练习。
not like it. We recommend practicing on strangers. They don't have a baseline and
到这个阶段，你可能很难想象
can accept you at face value. At this point, it may be hard for you to conceive
我很遗憾地说，许多美国人会因此不再愿意听你说话。
how differently you'll be treated. A lot of Americans, I regret to say, turn off
听到外国口音时就不想再听，或者态度不太友善。既然我们无法改变所有人，
when they hear a foreign accent or are less than kind. Since we can't change all
我们可以在你身上做一点小改变。
of them, we can make a small change in you.